{
    "id": "33695cac1b004bf3b538627fd6484eaa",
    "title": "Gap Filling Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "She is a ………………………… old lady.",
            "description": "Respectable means worthy of respect. ",
            "answers": [
                "respectful",
                "respectable"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9d7c96b59d5043759274662a72856194"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is very …………………………. I am sure he will succeed in life.",
            "description": "Industrious means skillful.",
            "answers": [
                "industrial",
                "industrious"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "911e3b37d8334e40a1a924f959949de8"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must learn to …………………………. yourself to changing circumstances.",
            "description": "To adapt is to adjust.",
            "answers": [
                "adapt",
                "adopt"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f684a851ac39455b84399c9a9874c85c"
        },
        {
            "question": "How long have you ………………………. in bed?",
            "description": "Lain is the past participle of to lie. ",
            "answers": [
                "lied",
                "lay",
                "lain"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b7ef0b1d7a25442691718c0237f5f67b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The project will require a …………………………….. amount of money.",
            "description": "Considerable means huge. ",
            "answers": [
                "considerable",
                "considerate"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "96e464ead0e94e5bbfbf7e63568ecac9"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was ……………………………. and lent me his car when I requested him to.",
            "description": "Considerate means thoughtful of others' feelings. ",
            "answers": [
                "considerable",
                "considerate"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8db5c5df04bf425baed3b7f59fc4987a"
        },
        {
            "question": "The speech was …………………………… uninspiring.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rather",
                "fairly"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9307af60f53a409793e8d0885864ec7d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The soldiers fired …………………………….. causing several civilians to die.",
            "description": "Indiscriminately means thoughtlessly. ",
            "answers": [
                "discriminately",
                "indiscriminately"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "980c0230c48a49e6a91276440e86cdff"
        },
        {
            "question": "She sat there, deep in …………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "thinking",
                "thought"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "905ff798a3bf49c3bccb98fc71eae90f"
        },
        {
            "question": "A good leader should be …………………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "apathetic",
                "sympathetic",
                "empathetic"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "08dec4db3646484a917b116aafd4aa37"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a …………………………… criminal.",
            "description": "A convicted criminal is one who is found guilty of committing a crime. ",
            "answers": [
                "convinced",
                "convicted"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "11f6cb8642774ff084940061a2680c18"
        },
        {
            "question": "The view from the window was ……………………………",
            "description": "Expansive means having a wide range. ",
            "answers": [
                "expensive",
                "expansive",
                "expulsive"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bc7e5698d0b34b27b4dbcbc39d7e47bf"
        }
    ]
}